const stuff = [
  { question: '10 - 10', answer: '0' },
  { question: '11 - 10', answer: '1' },
  { question: '12 - 10', answer: '2' },
  { question: '13 - 10', answer: '3' },
  { question: '14 - 10', answer: '4' },
  { question: '15 - 10', answer: '5' },
  { question: '16 - 10', answer: '6' },
  { question: '17 - 10', answer: '7' },
  { question: '18 - 10', answer: '8' },
  { question: '19 - 10', answer: '9' },
  { question: '20 - 10', answer: '10' },
  { question: '21 - 10', answer: '11' },
  { question: '22 - 10', answer: '12' },
  { question: '23 - 10', answer: '13' },
  { question: '24 - 10', answer: '14' },
  { question: '25 - 10', answer: '15' },
  { question: '26 - 10', answer: '16' },
  { question: '27 - 10', answer: '17' },
  { question: '28 - 10', answer: '18' },
  { question: '29 - 10', answer: '19' },
  { question: '30 - 10', answer: '20' },
  { question: '31 - 10', answer: '21' },
  { question: '32 - 10', answer: '22' },
  { question: '33 - 10', answer: '23' },
  { question: '34 - 10', answer: '24' },
  { question: '35 - 10', answer: '25' },
  { question: '36 - 10', answer: '26' },
  { question: '37 - 10', answer: '27' },
  { question: '38 - 10', answer: '28' },
  { question: '39 - 10', answer: '29' },
  { question: '40 - 10', answer: '30' },
  { question: '41 - 10', answer: '31' },
  { question: '42 - 10', answer: '32' },
  { question: '43 - 10', answer: '33' },
  { question: '44 - 10', answer: '34' },
  { question: '45 - 10', answer: '35' },
  { question: '46 - 10', answer: '36' },
  { question: '47 - 10', answer: '37' },
  { question: '48 - 10', answer: '38' },
  { question: '49 - 10', answer: '39' },
  { question: '50 - 10', answer: '40' },
  { question: '51 - 10', answer: '41' },
  { question: '52 - 10', answer: '42' },
  { question: '53 - 10', answer: '43' },
  { question: '54 - 10', answer: '44' },
  { question: '55 - 10', answer: '45' },
  { question: '56 - 10', answer: '46' },
  { question: '57 - 10', answer: '47' },
  { question: '58 - 10', answer: '48' },
  { question: '59 - 10', answer: '49' },
  { question: '60 - 10', answer: '50' },
]

export default stuff
